Guide to the Records of the Office of Media Production RG.7.3.4
New York University Archives
Records of the Office of Media Production
1983-2010
New York University Archives
New York University
New York University. Office of Media Production
RG.7.3.4
226 Linear Feet in 226 record cartons.
The Office of Media Production was established to create digital communication strategies to advance recruitment, development and public relations. This collection of recordings include promotional material, commencement footage and documentary footage of speakers, visitors and events. Tapes range in date from 1983 to 2010.
Conditions Governing Access
Repository permission is required for access. Please contact NYU Special Collections, special.collections@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Arrangement
Materials are arranged into two series:
Series I: Projects
Series II. 2025 Accretion
Historical Note
The Office of Media Production was established to create digital communication strategies to advance recruitment, development and public relations. It consults on, conceives, and produces video content for departments and schools for a variety of purposes. The office began in an informal capacity when Elisa Guarino began producing video works for the Office of the Vice President of External Affairs in the early 1980s. It became an official University operation circa 1987 and remained under External Affairs until NYU President John Sexton later brought the department under the auspices of the Office of University Relations and Public Affairs, which is responsible for portraying NYU's message, agenda, and image to external and internal audiences.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The videotapes in this collection were transferred in multiple accessions to the University Archives by the Office of Media Production, formerly under the authority of the Senior Vice President for External Affairs and presently reporting to the Senior Vice President for University Relations and Public Affairs. In November 2025, Nathan Townes-Anderson transferred an accretion of 118 Betacam SP tapes. The accession numbers associated with these transfers are 13.037, 14.049, 15.029, 2019.006, 2020.016, 2023.015, and 2025.043.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Access to some audiovisual materials in this collection is available through digitized access copies. Researchers may view an item's original container, but the media themselves are not available for playback because of preservation concerns. Materials that have already been digitized are noted in the collection's finding aid and can be requested in our reading room.
Audiovisual materials that have not been preserved may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact the New York University Archives, special.collections@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596 with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Scope and Contents
The audiovisual recordings in this collection contain promotional productions, University commencement ceremonies, lectures, panel discussions, and other events as well as B-roll footage of the NYU campus, study abroad sites and other New York City locations. The tapes comprise approximately 500 projects produced by the Office of Media Production.
Videocassettes.; New York (N.Y.).; Betacam-SP.; Commencement ceremonies; Commercials.; New York University. Office of Media Production; New York University. Gallatin Division; New York University. Tisch School of the Arts. George Amberg Memorial Film Study Center; Leonard N. Stern School of Business
- Series I: Projects
  Arrangement
  Materials are arranged by project number within each box or set of boxes.
  - NYU: Life in Greenwich Village (Reels 1-20), 1992-1998 (Box 1, Folder Project 1)
  - NYU: Life in Greenwich Village (Reels 21-32, 34-39), 1990-1994 (Box 2, Folder Project 1)
  - Vaclav Havel at NYU (Reels 1-3, 5-7), undated (Box 3, Folder Project 2)
  - NYU in Prague Video (Reels 1-8), undated (Box 3, Folder Project 3)
  - Boris Yeltsin at NYU (Reels 1-6), undated (Box 3, Folder Project 4)
  - Oliva Inauguration Video (Reels 1-14), undated (Box 4, Folder Project 5)
  - Commencement 1991 (Reels 1-20) (Box 5, Folder Project 6)
  - Commencement 1991 (Reels 21-37) (Box 6, Folder Project 6)
  - Commencement 1991 (Reels 38-46) (Box 7, Folder Project 6)
  - La Pietra Video (Reels 1-40, 87), undated (Box 8, Folder Project 7)
  - La Pietra Video (Reels 41-70), undated (Box 9, Folder Project 7)
  - La Pietra Video (Reels 71-86), undated (Box 10, Folder Project 7)
  - La Pietra Video (Reels 88-102), undated (Box 11, Folder Project 7)
  - La Pietra Video (Reels 103-117), undated (Box 12, Folder Project 7)
  - La Pietra Video (Reels 118-135), undated (Box 13, Folder Project 7)
  - La Pietra Video (Reels 136-153, 157-163, 165-167, 170, 172, 173), undated (Box 14, Folder Project 7)
  - Andreotti at NYU (Reels 1-4), undated (Box 15, Folder Project 8)
  - Commencement 1993 (Reels 1-17) (Box 16, Folder Project 9)
  - Commencement 1993 (Reels 18-33) (Box 17, Folder Project 9)
  - Commencement 1993 (Reels 34-49) (Box 18, Folder Project 9)
  - Commencement 1993 (Reels 50-64) (Box 19, Folder Project 9)
  - Prime Minister Reynolds at NYU (Reels 1-4), undated (Box 19, Folder Project 10)
  - Lee Brown at NYU (Reels 1-3), undated (Box 20, Folder Project 11)
  - Onassis Center Video (Reels 1-6), undated (Box 20, Folder Project 12)
  - Prime Minister Kaifu at NYU (Reels 1-4, 6-10), undated (Box 20, Folder Project 13)
  - Weehawken Press Conference (Reels 1-3), undated (Box 20, Folder Project 14)
  - NYU Watch Team Video (Reels 1-13), undated (Box 21, Folder Project 15)
  - Students and Jobs (Reels 1-31), undated (Box 22, Folder Project 16)
  - Students and Jobs (Reels 32-40), undated (Box 23, Folder Project 16)
  - Mrs. Cuomo Event (Reels 1-7), undated (Box 23, Folder Project 17)
  - CAS TA Seminar (Reels 1-5), undated (Box 23, Folder Project 18)
  - Casa Italiana Dedication (Reels 1-6, Audio Reel), undated (Box 24, Folder Project 19)
  - Prime Minister Haughey at NYU (Reels 1-4), undated (Box 24, Folder Project 20)
  - Poetry Reading Video (Reels 1-3, 5), undated (Box 24, Folder Project 21)
  - Faculty Resource Network Video (Reels 1-20), undated (Box 25, Folder Project 22)
  - Faculty Resource Network Video (Reels 21-38), undated (Box 26, Folder Project 22)
  - Faculty Resource Network Video (Reels 39-51), undated (Box 27, Folder Project 22)
  - Commencement 1995 (Reels 1-23) (Box 28, Folder Project 23)
  - Commencement 1995 (Reels 24-46) (Box 29, Folder Project 23)
  - Commencement 1990 (Reels 1-18) (Box 30, Folder Project 24)
  - Commencement 1989 (Reels 1-7) (Box 31, Folder Project: 25)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend (Reels 1-5), undated (Box 31, Folder Project: 26)
  - Myra Alperson at FAS Journalism (Reel 1), undated (Box 31, Folder Project: 27)
  - Alumni Hall Video (Reels 1-10, 12, 13), 1991 (Box 32, Folder Project: 28)
  - NYC Street Scenes (Reels 1-3), undated (Box 32, Folder Project: 29)
  - NYU in Albany Day (Reels -12), undated (Box 33, Folder Project: 30)
  - Mario Cuomo at NYU (Reels 1-3), undated (Box 33, Folder Project: 31)
  - Dental Center Graduation 1994 (Reels 1-10) (Box 34, Folder Project: 32)
  - Russian Tea Room Lectures (Reels 1-17), undated (Box 35, Folder Project: 33)
  - Russian Tea Room Lectures (Reels 18-35), undated (Box 36, Folder Project: 33)
  - Russian Tea Room Lectures (Reels 36-44), undated (Box 37, Folder Project: 33)
  - Commencement 1992 (Reels 1-15) (Box 38, Folder Project: 34)
  - Commencement 1992 (Reels 16-34) (Box 39, Folder Project: 34)
  - Commencement 1992 (Reels 35-38) (Box 40, Folder Project: 34)
  - NYU Music Sing-a-long (Reels 1-5), undated (Box 40, Folder Project: 37)
  - Stephen J Gould Lecture (Reels 1-5), undated (Box 40, Folder Project: 38)
  - Stern Lecture with Harvey Golub (Reels 1-5), undated (Box 40, Folder Project: 39)
  - Stern Lecture with Sidney Harmon (Reels 1-8), undated (Box 41, Folder Project: 40)
  - Stern Lecture with Christie Hefner (Reels 1-9), undated (Box 41, Folder Project: 41)
  - Stern Lecture with Jack Welsh (Reels 1-5), undated (Box 41, Folder Project: 42)
  - Ireland House Dedication (Reels 1-19), undated (Box 42, Folder Project: 43)
  - Ireland House Dedication (Reels 20-28), undated (Box 43, Folder Project: 43)
  - Irish Muse (Reels 1-4), undated (Box 43, Folder Project: 44)
  - Irish Prime Minister at NYU (Reels 1-2), undated (Box 43, Folder Project: 45)
  - Irish Prime Minister Albert Reynolds Address to NYU (Reels 1), undated (Box 43, Folder Project: 46)
  - Going to College - Video News Release (Reels 1-17), 1992 (Box 44, Folder Project: 47)
  - Going to College - Video News Release (Reels 18-30), 1992 (Box 45, Folder Project: 47)
  - Onassis Center Gold Medal for Excellence (Reels 1-4), undated (Box 45, Folder Project: 48)
  - Inside New York University (Reels 1-4), undated (Box 46, Folder Project: 49)
  - Commencement 1996 (Reels 2-8) (Box 46, Folder Project: 50)
  - Chet Huntley Memorial Lecture Series (Reels 1-8), undated (Box 47, Folder Project: 52)
  - The Tradition Continues: NYU's 14th President (Reels 1-22), undated (Box 48, Folder Project: 53)
  - Billion Dollar Gala Video (Reels 1-12, 14-17, 18(missing), 19-25, 27, 29-25), undated (Box 48, Folder Project: 118)
  - Million Dollar A Plate Dinner at NYU (Reel 1), undated (Box 48, Folder Project: 119)
  - Wagner Graduate School of Public Service (Reels 1-17), undated (Box 49, Folder Project: 54)
  - Wagner Graduate School of Public Service (Reels 18-29), undated (Box 50, Folder Project: 54)
  - Rita Sussmuth at NYU (Reels 1-3), undated (Box 51, Folder Project: 55)
  - All University Dinner Dance (Reels 1-2), undated (Box 51, Folder Project: 56)
  - Benefactors' Luncheon (Reels 1-9), undated (Box 51, Folder Project: 57)
  - John Brademas, President, NYU (Reel 1), undated (Box 51, Folder Project: 58)
  - NYU B-roll (Reels 1-9), undated (Box 52, Folder Project: 59)
  - Musical Theatre Hall of Fame 1993 (Reels 1-6) (Box 52, Folder Project: 60)
  - Musical Theatre Hall of Fame 1994 (Reels 1-10) (Box 53, Folder Project: 61)
  - NYU in the News (Reels 1-2), undated (Box 53, Folder Project: 62)
  - Convention 1992: NYU Faculty in the Media for the DNC (Reel 1) (Box 53, Folder Project: 63)
  - NYU in the Movies (Reels 1-8), undated (Box 53, Folder Project: 64)
  - Beat Conference (Project 0065), 1994 (Box 54, Folder Reels 1-16)
    Digital surrogates available
    All of the audiovisual materials created as a part of this project have been digitized. Please contact the University Archives for information regarding access to digitized audiovisual materials.
    - Pitch Reel Master, 1994 May 19; 1 U-matic (Box 54, Reel 1, Box Shared University Archives 106, Disc 13)
      Existence and Location of Copies
      Access copy available.
    - Pitch Reel Master, 1 DVD-R TRT: 00:07:32 (Box ACCESS 1, Disc 13)
    - Pitch Reel Dub, 1994; 1 U-matic (Box 54, Reel 2)
    - B-Roll, Town Hall Gala Poetry Reading and Concert, 1994 May 19; 1 U-matic (Box 54, Reel 3)
    - Marathon Reading, 1994 May 22; 1 Betacam (Box 206, Reel 4, Box Shared University Archives 106, Item 20)
    - Beat Generation Conference CBS/CNN, 1994; 3 VHS (Box 206, Reel 5-7, Box Shared University Archives 106, Disc 12)
    - Beat Generation Conference CBS/CNN, 1 CD-ROM TRT: 00:08:35 (Box ACCESS 1, Disc 12)
    - Beat Conference: Performance at Town Hall, 1994 May 19; 2 Hi8 (Box 54, Reel 8-9, Box Shared University Archives 106, Item 14-15)
    - Beat Conference: Rowe/McNeely Computer Jazz, 1992 November 2; 1 audiocassettes; While this tape is labeled Project 0065, it is not clear that this content relates to that project. (Box 54, Reel 10, Box Shared University Archives 106, Disc 10)
    - Beat Conference: Rowe/McNeely Computer Jazz, 1 CD-ROM (Box ACCESS 1, Disc 10)
    - Beat Conference: Beat Generation on NPR, 1994; 4 audiocassettes (Box 54, Reel 10-13)
    - Open Video without Titles and Close, 1994; 1 Betacam_SP (Box 206, Reel 14, Box Shared University Archives 106, Disc 11)
    - Town Hall Performance, 1994 May 19; 2 Betacam_SP; Production element: Beta Dub of Hi8 master. (Box 54, Reel 15-16)
  - Honorable Elected Carlos Salinas De Gortari Convocation (Reels 1-4), undated (Box 54, Folder Project: 66)
  - Ultra Violet (Reels 1-2), undated (Box 54, Folder Project: 67)
  - Francois Mitterand Convocation (Reels 1-2), undated (Box 54, Folder Project: 68)
  - School of Social Work Dedication (Reels 1-4), undated (Box 55, Folder Project: 69)
  - Salzberger Speech at Law School (Reels 1-4), undated (Box 55, Folder Project: 70)
  - NYU School of Law Video (Reels 1-43), undated; cuid19650 (Box 56, Folder Project: 71)
    - Reel 32: Professor Derrick Bell Interview, cuid19651 (Box 56, Betacam sp cuid19651)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Duration: 10 minutes.
  - NYU School of Law Video (Reels 44-101), undated (Box 57, Folder Project: 71)
  - NYU School of Law Video (Reels 102-144), undated (Box 58, Folder Project: 71)
  - NYU School of Law Video (Reels 145-169), undated (Box 59, Folder Project: 71)
  - Kathleen Turner at NYU (Reel 1), undated (Box 59, Folder Project: 72)
  - NYU Logo (Reels 1-4), undated (Box 60, Folder Project: 73)
  - Oliva at Senate Meeting (Reels 1-2), undated (Box 60, Folder Project: 74)
  - Crossing the Bridge: CAT at United Nations (Reels 1-3), undated (Box 60, Folder Project: 75)
  - Claire Fagin Lecture (Reels 1-5), undated (Box 60, Folder Project: 76)
  - Wagner: Global Connection (Reels 1-11), undated (Box 60, Folder Project: 77)
  - Stern CEO Series (Reels 1-3), undated (Box 60, Folder Project: 78)
  - Carl Bernstein at NYU (Reels 1-2), undated (Box 61, Folder Project: 79)
  - Law - Strengthening Democracy in a Global Economy (Reels 1-7), undated (Box 61, Folder Project: 81)
  - Laurence A. Tisch Gala (Reels 1-6), undated (Box 61, Folder Project 83)
  - Cantor Film Center Opening (Reels 1-3, 5), undated (Box 61, Folder Project 84)
  - Grad Alley 1997 (Reels 1-7) (Box 61, Folder Project 85)
  - Women's Basketball NCAA Final Four Dinner at Bobst (Tape 1), undated; cuid0 (Box 61, Folder Project 86, Box Shared University Archives 117, Item 8)
  - Women's Basketball NCAA Final Four Dinner at Bobst (Tape 2), cuid1 (Box 61, Folder 86, Box Shared University Archives 117, Item 9)
  - Distinguished Teaching Medal (Reel 1 - 22), 1999, undated (Box 62, Folder Project 87)
  - School of Law Campaign (Reel 1 - 22), 1999 (Box 62, Folder Project 88)
  - Brigadoon (Reel 1 - 5), 1999 (Box 62, Folder Project 89)
  - Brigadoon Master Tapes (Reel 1 - 2), 1999 (Box 63, Folder Project 89)
  - Gallatin Recruitment (Reel 1 - 47), 1995-1999 (Box 63, Folder Project 90)
  - Gallatin Recruitment (Reel 48 - 63), 1996-1999 (Box 64, Folder Project 90)
  - NYU Downtown Hospital (Reel 1 - 31), 1998 (Box 64, Folder Project 91)
  - Annual Survey of American Law Dedication (Reel 1 - 3), 1999 (Box 65, Folder Project 92)
  - Dental VNR on Oral Cancer Screenings (Reel 1 - 3), 1999 (Box 65, Folder Project 93)
  - Tribute to Bobby Wagner Event (Reel 1 - 4), 1999 (Box 65, Folder Project 95)
  - Stern Ug Pre-Commencement (Reel 1 - 10), 1998 (Box 65, Folder Project 186)
  - Stern Groundbreaking (Reel 1 - 7), 1990 (Box 65, Folder Project 99)
    - Groundbreaking Education at Stern, 1990; cuid18415 (Box 65, U-matic cuid18415)
      Duration: 9 minutes
    - Groundbreaking Tape 3 -- Allison and Leonard Stern, June 20, 1990; cuid18416 (Box 65, U-matic cuid18416)
      Duration: 11 minutes
  - Clinton Inaugural (Reel 1), 1993 (Box 66, Folder Project 101)
  - Dean Berne San Antonio Talk (Reel 1), 1995 (Box 66, Folder Project 102)
  - Dean Berne San Antonio Talk Master (Reel 1), 1995 (Box 66, Folder Project 102)
  - President Kim NYU School of Law (Reel 1), undated (Box 66, Folder Project 104)
  - Israel at 50 (Reel 1 - 4), 1998 (Box 66, Folder Project 105)
  - Tom Bishop's 25th Anniversary Reception Master (Reel 1), 1995 (Box 66, Folder Project 106)
  - Tom Bishop's 25th Anniversary Reception (Reel 1 - ), undated (Box 66, Folder Project 106)
  - Benefactor's Luncheon (Reel 1 - 3), 1994 (Box 66, Folder Project 108)
  - Commencement (Reel 1), 1986 (Box 66, Folder Project 109)
  - Commencement (Reel 1), 1987 (Box 66, Folder Project 110)
  - College of Dentistry Graduation (Reel 1 - 7), 1993 (Box 66, Folder Project 111)
  - Commencement (Reel 1 - 9), 1997 (Box 67, Folder Project 112)
  - College of Dentistry Graduation Master (Reel 1 - 2), 1997 (Box 67, Folder Project 113)
  - College of Dentistry Graduation (Reel 1 - 8), 1997 (Box 67, Folder Project 113)
  - Stern MBA Recruitment Video (Reel 45 - 58), 1995-1996 (Box 68, Folder Project 114)
  - Traditions/Tensions: Contemporary Art in Asia (Reel 1 - 7), undated (Box 68, Folder Project 137)
  - Stern MBA Commencement Video (Reel 1 - 9), 1998 (Box 69, Folder Project 115)
  - Stern MBA Commencement Video (Reel 1 - 10, 12) ), 1998-1999 (Box 69, Folder Project 116)
  - Stern MBA Commencement Video (Reel 1 - 25, 29), 1996 (Box 69, Folder Project 117)
  - Stern MBA Commencement Video Master, 1996 (Box 69, Folder Project 117)
  - Stern MBA Commencement Video Master Dub, 1996 (Box 69, Folder Project 117)
  - Billion Dollar Gala (Reel 1 - 35, 50, 53, and 59), 1991-1995 (Box 70, Folder Project 118)
  - Billion Dollar Gala Master (Reel 1), undated (Box 70, Folder Project 118)
  - Billion Dollar Gala (Reel 36 -48, 52, 54 - 63) ), undated (Box 71, Folder Project 118)
  - Billion Dollar Gala Video News Release (Reel 1 - 4), 1995 (Box 71, Folder Project 120)
  - Billion Dollar Gala Archival Coverage of Event (Reel 1 - 5), 1995 (Box 71, Folder Project 121)
  - Billion Dollar Gala: Acton Medalist Video (Reel 1 - 4), undated (Box 71, Folder Project 122)
  - C-Team Cabaret and Silent Auction Master (Reel 1 - 2), 1999 (Box 206, Folder Project 124)
  - C-Team Cabaret and Silent Auction (Reel 1 - 5), 1999 (Box 71, Folder Project 124, Reel 1-3, Box 206, Reel 4-5)
  - Laurence Tisch Tribute Video (Reel 1 - 36), 1999 (Box 72, Folder Project 125)
  - Laurence Tisch Tribute Audio Tapes (Reel 37 - 43), 1999 (Box 72, Folder Project 125)
  - Laurence Tisch Tribute Video Master Tapes (45 - 47), 1999 (Box 72, Folder Project 125)
  - Commencement, 1995 (Box 73, Folder Project 23)
  - Commencement Master, 1995 (Box 73, Folder Project 23)
  - Stern Ug Pre-Commencement Ceremony (Reel 1 - 10), 1999 (Box 73, Folder Project 98)
  - Chubb Breakfast (Reel 1 - 2), 1999 (Box 73, Folder Project 126)
  - Hertzberg Lecture (Reel 1 - 3), 1995 (Box 73, Folder Project 127)
  - DiPietro Lecture (Reel 1 - 3), 1994 (Box 73, Folder Project 128)
  - Y2K New Year (Reel 1), 1999 (Box 73, Folder Project 129)
  - Grad Alley (Reel 1 - 3), 1999 (Box 73, Folder Project 130)
  - America Jewish Congress (Reel 1 - 3), 1997 (Box 73, Folder Project 131)
  - Bronfman Center Dedication Master (Reel 1), 1996; cuid17543 (Box 73, Folder Project 132)
    Duration: 56 minutes
  - Bronfman Center Dedication (Reel 1 - 5), 1996 (Box 73, Folder Project 132)
  - King Hussein of Jordan at NYU, 1996 (Box 73, Folder Project 134)
    - King Hussein of Jordan at NYU Tape 1, 1996 (Box 73, Folder Project 134, Reel 1)
      Technical requirements
      Original format: Betacam SP, Sony stock
    - King Hussein of Jordan at NYU Tape 2, 1996 (Box 73, Folder Project 134, Reel 2)
    - King Hussein of Jordan at NYU Tape 3, 1996 (Box 73, Folder Project 134, Reel 3)
    - King Hussein of Jordan at NYU Tape 4, 1996 (Box 73, Folder Project 134, Reel 4)
    - King Hussein of Jordan at NYU: Set-up Tape 5, 1996 (Box 73, Folder Project 134, Reel 5)
    - King Hussein of Jordan at NYU: Various B-roll, King's dinner remarks Tape 6, 1996 (Box 73, Folder Project 134, Reel 6)
  - Rector's Conference (Reel 1 - 30), 1997 (Box 74, Folder Project 135)
  - The Stern Follies (Reel 1 - 8), 1994 (Box 74, Folder Project 136)
  - TSOA Salute (Reel 1 - 5), 1998 (Box 75, Folder Project 138)
  - TSOA Salute Master (Reel 1), 1998 (Box 75, Folder Project 138)
  - Future Filmmakers Workshop Dub of Master (Reel 7), undated (Box 75, Folder Project 139)
  - TSOA Salute 1998 Graduation Roll (Box 75, Folder Project 140)
  - United Athletic Association 10th Anniversary (Reel 1 - 29), 1986-1996 (Box 75, Folder Project 141)
  - United Athletic Association 10th Anniversary Master 3 Reel), 1986-1996 (Box 75, Folder Project 141)
  - United Athletic Association 10th Anniversary (Reel 33 - 58), undated (Box 76, Folder Project 141)
  - Development Breakfast (Reel 1 - 2), 1997 (Box 77, Folder Project 142)
  - Rector's Conference (Reel 1 - 30), 1995 (Box 77, Folder Project 143)
  - New York Times Writing Fellows (Reel 1 - 2), undated (Box 77, Folder Project 144)
  - New York Times Writing Fellows Master (Reel 1), 1995 (Box 77, Folder Project 144)
  - Stern Haskins Partners Dinner (Reel 1 - 3), 1997 (Box 77, Folder Project 145)
  - Equal Seminar (Reel 1 - 6), 1995 (Box 77, Folder Project 146)
  - Stern Women's Lecture Series: "A Conversation with 3 Accomplished Women" Master (Reel 1), undated (Box 78, Folder Project 147)
  - Stern Women's Lecture Series: "A Conversation with 3 Accomplished Women" (Reel 1 - 3), 1997 (Box 78, Folder Project 147)
  - Stern Alumni Outreach Month: "Essence of Entrepreneurship" Master (Reel 1), 1997 (Box 78, Folder Project 148)
  - Stern Alumni Outreach Month: "Essence of Entrepreneurship" (Reel 1 - 3), undated (Box 78, Folder Project 148)
  - Stern Lecture Series: "When the Shoe No Longer Fits: Job Change or Career Change" Master (Reel 1), 1997 (Box 78, Folder Project 149)
  - Stern Lecture Series: "When the Shoe No Longer Fits: Job Change or Career Change" (Reel 1 - 2), 1997 (Box 78, Folder Project 149)
  - Stern Lecture Series: "The Impact of Mergers and Acquisitions on the Financial Services" Master (Reel 1), 1997 (Box 78, Folder Project 150)
  - Stern Lecture Series: "The Impact of Mergers and Acquisitions on the Financial Services" (Reel 3), 1997 (Box 78, Folder Project 150)
  - President's Service Awards (Reel 1 - 3(, 1996 (Box 78, Folder Project 151)
  - Shimon Peres at NYU (Reel 1 - 5), 1994 (Box 78, Folder Project 152)
  - NYU in France (Reel 1 - 16), 1994 (Box 78, Folder Project 153)
  - NYU in France (Reel 17 - 29), 1994 (Box 79, Folder Project 153)
  - NYU in France Master (Reel 1), 1994 (Box 79, Folder Project 153)
  - NYU in France Protection Master (Reel 1), 1994 (Box 79, Folder Project 153)
  - Audio Tapes, 1994 (Box 79, Folder Project 154)
  - Urban Business Assistance Corporation (Reel 1 - 12), 1994 (Box 79, Folder Project 154)
  - Lillian Vernon Center (Reel 1 - 2), 1999 (Box 79, Folder Project 155)
  - Rector's Conference (Reel 1 - 32), 1999 (Box 80, Folder Project 156)
  - Commencement (Reel 1 - 7), 1998 (Box 81, Folder Project 157)
  - Commencement Master (Reel 1 - 4, 12), 1998 (Box 81, Folder Project 157)
  - School of Law Debate (Reel 1 - 8), 1997 (Box 81, Folder Project 158)
  - School of Law Debate Master (Reel 1), 1997 (Box 81, Folder Project 158)
  - Musical Theatre Hall of Fame (Reel 1 - 13), 1996 (Box 81, Folder Project 159)
  - Musical Theatre Hall of Fame Master (Reel 1), 1996 (Box 81, Folder Project 159)
  - Dental School Recruitment Video (Reel 1 - 21), 1996 (Box 82, Folder Project 162)
  - Dental School Graduation Master (Reel 1 - 2), 1998 (Box 82, Folder Project 163)
  - Dental School Graduation (Reel 1 - 11), 1998 (Box 82, Folder Project 163)
  - Dental School Graduation, 1992 (Box 82, Folder Project 164)
  - American Benefactor Remaster (1 Reel), 1995 (Box 82, Folder Project 165)
  - Dental School Graduation (Reel 1 - 10), 1999 (Box 82, Folder Project 166)
  - A View From Ireland House Master (Reel 1), undated (Box 83, Folder Project 161)